

Sviatoslav Tyshchyk

Front-end developer

svet.tyshchyk@gmail.com

https://github.com/STyshchyk

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/svyurie/

(a) https://www.instagram.com/sv.yurie/

(L) +380682372585

My Contact

Education

Ukrainian National Forestry University

Bachelor in Forestry Engineering 2013-2017

Project and achievements

- 3D scanning in Forestry
- Second place in annual University conference
- Ukrainian National Forestry University

Master in Forestry Engineering 2013-2019

Project and achievements

- · Second place in annual University conference
- Graduated from the university with honors
- Front-end at https://rs.school/
- Insititute Of Leadership, Management And Coaching

Soft Skill

Negotiation Adaptability

Problem-solving

Time management

2022 - Present Professional coach

Hard Skill

- CSS3/HTML5
- JavaScript
- Git
- Bootstrap
- React
- SQL

About Me

I have been working as a developer for MetaTrader for the last 3 years on a freelance basis, Upwork mainly. I developed various trading robots/scripts that simplify trading. Developing was performed using MQL language, it's very similar to C++.. Also, I have experience in QA, I worked for Gameloft company in 2019 in Lviv's office.

Professional Experience

QA tester at Gameloft 2019-2019

Team of 14 people Project: Asphalt 9

Responsibilities:

- · Collaboration with developers and team
- **Analyze Specifications**
- **Execute Tests**
- Document Bugs
- · Troubleshoot Issues

MQL developer/Freelancer Upwork 2019 - present

Responsibilities:

- Gather info from clients regarding products.
- Negotiated and consult technical aspects
- Create a documentation
- Developing and maintenance
- Make sure that client's expectations are met

Tools & Technologies:

MQ4, MQ5, Telegram API, C++, SQLite, Pine Script

Languages

- Ukrainian: native
- **English: Intermediate**